const DATA = [
    {
      question: 'What was the main character’s nickname in The Sword in the Stone?',
      answers: [
        'Wart',
        'Arthur',
        'General Zod',
        'Yabba Dooba Zeeba'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Wart',
      icon: 'https://66.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m1is89bGXm1rn95k2o1_500.gif',
      icon2: 'https://everydayterrors.files.wordpress.com/2014/10/arieldisappointed.gif',
      alt: 'feedback logo'
    },
    {
      question: 'What animal does Jafar turn into in his duel against Aladdin?',
      answers: [
        'Cobra',
        'A yellow crying monkey',
        'An ogre that will squish the jelly from your eyes',
        'An old man'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Cobra',
        icon: 'https://66.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m1is89bGXm1rn95k2o1_500.gif',
        icon2: 'https://everydayterrors.files.wordpress.com/2014/10/arieldisappointed.gif',
        alt: 'feedback logo'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where did Mufasa and his lions live in throughout the movie The Lion King?',
      answers: [
        'Pride Rock',
        'Pleasure Island',
        'Fortress of Solitude',
        'The Millenium Falcon'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Pride Rock',
        icon: 'https://66.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m1is89bGXm1rn95k2o1_500.gif',
        icon2: 'https://everydayterrors.files.wordpress.com/2014/10/arieldisappointed.gif',
        alt: 'feedback logo'
    },
    {
      question: 'What did Luke want to do before he took the droids to get them cleaned up in Star Wars: A New Hope?',
      answers: [
        'Go to toshi station to pick up some power converters',
        'Thank the Maker',
        'Drink some blue milk',
        'Bullseye Womp Rats in his T-16'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Go to toshi station to pick up some power converters',
      icon: 'https://66.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m1is89bGXm1rn95k2o1_500.gif',
      icon2: 'https://everydayterrors.files.wordpress.com/2014/10/arieldisappointed.gif',
      alt: 'feedback logo'
    },
    {
      question: 'Hercules had to give up his god strength for the sake of Megara’s life.  How long was this duration?',
      answers: [
        '24 hours',
        '4 weeks: a month if its February',
        '3 days',
        'a week'
        ],
      correctAnswer: '24 hours',
      icon: 'https://66.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m1is89bGXm1rn95k2o1_500.gif',
      icon2: 'https://everydayterrors.files.wordpress.com/2014/10/arieldisappointed.gif',
      alt: 'feedback logo'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where/when was the time period of the novel that Hunchback of Notre Dame is based on?',
      answers: [
        'Paris, 1482',
        'London, 2011',
        'Russia, 1917',
        'None of the above'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Paris, 1482',
      icon: 'https://66.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m1is89bGXm1rn95k2o1_500.gif',
      alt: 'feedback logo'
    },
    {
      question: 'The stray cat that the Aristocats meet is known as: O’malley the ____ ?',
      answers: [
      'stray cat',
      'tap dancing cat',
      'alley cat',
      'jazzy cat'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'alley cat',
      icon: 'https://66.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m1is89bGXm1rn95k2o1_500.gif',
      icon2: 'https://everydayterrors.files.wordpress.com/2014/10/arieldisappointed.gif',
      alt: 'feedback logo'
    },
    {
      question: 'What food was Lady and Tramp eating when they accidentally kissed?',
      answers: [
        'Pesto cavatappi',
        'Spaghetti and meatballs',
        'Wonton Soup',
        'Chips'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Spaghetti and meatballs',
      icon: 'https://66.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m1is89bGXm1rn95k2o1_500.gif',
      icon2: 'https://everydayterrors.files.wordpress.com/2014/10/arieldisappointed.gif',
      alt: 'feedback logo'
    },
    {
      question: 'How did Simba describe the food that Timon and Pumba gave him?',
      answers: [
      'A thing to kill for.',
      'Real but fake.',
      'Oingo and Boingo.',
      'Slimy yet satisfying.'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Slimy yet satisfying.',
      icon: 'https://66.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m1is89bGXm1rn95k2o1_500.gif',
      icon2: 'https://everydayterrors.files.wordpress.com/2014/10/arieldisappointed.gif',
      alt: 'feedback logo'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which Disney Princess wears a green dress?',
      answers: [
        'Princess Fiona',
        'Princess Tiana',
        'Princess Kida',
        'Princess Bride'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Princess Tiana',
    icon: 'https://66.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m1is89bGXm1rn95k2o1_500.gif',
    icon2: 'https://everydayterrors.files.wordpress.com/2014/10/arieldisappointed.gif',
    alt: 'feedback logo'
    }
];
